<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Tech &#8211; Sukanta Pal</title>
	<atom:link href="https://blog.sukantapal.com/category/tech/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://blog.sukantapal.com/</link>
	<description>Reading Room</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 12:39:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://blog.sukantapal.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/cropped-Master-blog-sukantapal-Site-icon_ONLY-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Tech &#8211; Sukanta Pal</title>
	<link>https://blog.sukantapal.com/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Microsoft TechVista 2014 at Jaipur INDIA</title>
		<link>https://blog.sukantapal.com/microsoft-techvista-2014-at-jaipur-india/</link>
					<comments>https://blog.sukantapal.com/microsoft-techvista-2014-at-jaipur-india/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sukanta Pal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Tech]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.sukantapal.com/?p=463</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Microsoft Research India has selected the pink city Jaipur, the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-justify">Microsoft Research India has selected the pink city Jaipur, the capital of Rajasthan States of India for this year&#8217;s 9th annual research symposium Tech Event called <strong>Microsoft TechVista 2014</strong>. </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="2048" height="1360" src="https://blog.sukantapal.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Microsoft-TechVista-2014-Jaipur-Group-Photo.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-460"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Microsoft TechVista 2014 Jaipur Group Photo.</figcaption></figure>



<p class="has-text-align-justify">It was filled with Global Research Leaders. Tech Vista offers a great chance for the Government, universal research community and students to interrelate and share innovative ideas on research and its upcoming routes.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="1600" height="1200" src="https://blog.sukantapal.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Sukanta33298_Sukanta-Pal_LR.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-461"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Microsoft TechVista Event Badge &#038; Wrist Band. Photograph: Sukanta Pal | sukantapal.com</figcaption></figure>



<p class="has-text-align-justify">Here assembled the first-rate computing researchers, governmental leaders, and talented academics. It was a most excellent platform to work together and swap over ideas while conversing about the function of Computer Science in the year 2014. The Microsoft Tech event was held on <strong>24th January 2014, Friday</strong> between 8:30 am &#8211; 6:30 pm at Deep Smriti Auditorium, Tagore International School in Jaipur, Rajasthan.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="2048" height="1360" src="https://blog.sukantapal.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Computer-Scientist-P.-Anandan-Padmanabhan-Anandan.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-462"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Computer Scientist P. Anandan (Padmanabhan Anandan).</figcaption></figure>



<p><strong>TechVista 2014 Speakers and Summary of their speech:</strong></p>



<ol>
<li><strong>Jeannette Wing: </strong>The Impact of Computer Science Research on Technology, Science, and civilization-</li>
</ol>



<p class="has-text-align-justify">The meadow of computing is steered by technological modernism, societal requirements and scientific queries. There is an amazing relationship, push &amp; pull among these 3 drivers. That is to say, picking up the pace in technological progressions and colossal societal demands compels civilizations to re-examine the most essential scientific queries of computing. These drivers are also events of the impact of computing research. Jeannette wqs offering some instances from the Microsoft Research and their impact on technology, society and science. She was direct the batons to innovative directions for computing research.</p>



<p><strong>2. Hsiao-Wuen Hon:</strong> Datafication of the globe: Populace &amp; Physical Spac-</p>



<p class="has-text-align-justify">Despite the fact that Big Data has developed into an well-liked phrase in the modern day, Hsiao-Wuen Hon was talk about the ways to use data to a better model, understand, and symbolize the globes repeated process all over the ages. Data lets people to construct models to comprehend the ways through which the globe operates, so that they can make enhanced forecasts and judgments and see the earth from new fangled standpoints. He was also investigate projects from the Microsoft Research in Beijing in the topics of graphics, urban informatics and human computer interaction to exemplify the ways through which the data offer new and better-off means to connect with citizens and the substantial space.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="960" height="540" src="https://blog.sukantapal.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Audience.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-459"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Packed Audience of Microsoft TechVista 2014 Event.</figcaption></figure>



<p>3. <strong>Curtis Wong:</strong> From the border of the Universe and the flipside-</p>



<p>Curtis talk was wrap up the conception of the Worldwide Telescope to envisage the Universe served as the groundwork to research more intricate energetic data sets and its guided expedition was lend a hand in democratize access and perceptive of spatial chronological information for people on the Earth.</p>



<p>4. <strong>Chris Bishop:</strong> Probabilistic Models &amp; Machine Learning-</p>



<p>Chris’s speech was commence the major ideas of computing with indecision, and explained with tutorial instances and real-world case revisions.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" loading="lazy" width="2592" height="1802" src="https://blog.sukantapal.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/240120141020_Sukanta_Sukanta-Pal_LR.webp" alt="" class="wp-image-458"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Sukanta Pal at Microsoft TechVista 2014 Jaipur Event.</figcaption></figure>



<p>5. <strong>Bill Thies: </strong>Real time audience survey or polling with computer vision-</p>



<p>In his speech, Bill explained the experience piloting the computer vision technology in the schools of Bangalore.</p>



<p><strong>Media Resources</strong></p>



<ol>
<li>Microsoft Research India Facebook <a href="https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.703282243045587&amp;type=3" target="_blank" aria-label="Album (opens in a new tab)" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="ek-link">Album</a></li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://blog.sukantapal.com/microsoft-techvista-2014-at-jaipur-india/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
