<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Fashion &#8211; Sukanta Pal</title>
	<atom:link href="https://https://sukantapal.github.io/blog/category/fashion/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://https://sukantapal.github.io/blog/</link>
	<description>Reading Room</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 08:44:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://https://sukantapal.github.io/blog/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/cropped-Master-blog-sukantapal-Site-icon_ONLY-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Fashion &#8211; Sukanta Pal</title>
	<link>https://https://sukantapal.github.io/blog/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Men’s Essential Type of Bags</title>
		<link>https://https://sukantapal.github.io/blog/mens-essential-type-of-bags/</link>
					<comments>https://https://sukantapal.github.io/blog/mens-essential-type-of-bags/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sukanta Pal]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 08:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Fashion]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://https://sukantapal.github.io/blog/?p=296</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Most essential types of bags for men in the Year...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p class="has-text-align-justify">Most essential types of bags for men in the Year 2022 list down, everyday men&#8217;s activities and type of work with style bag industry shape in large. When it comes to fashion, accessories are as essential as clothing. A good-looking bag can make your casual outfits also look super stylish. As men&#8217;s fashion evolves constantly, there are a few styles of bags that are here to stay. Bags aren&#8217;t overlooked and labeled as a women&#8217;s accessory anymore. More and more bag styles emerge for men&#8217;s functional and fashion needs. Here are 5 Types Of Bags Every Man Needs To Add Functionality To His Wardrobe.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="DELHI TO MANALI VLOVO BUS by IntrCity Smart Bus" width="720" height="405" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9UH2A9cuLFU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div><figcaption>Himachal Trip with Backpack. Film: Sukanta Pal | sukantapal.com</figcaption></figure>



<ol><li>BACKPACK&nbsp; &#8211;&nbsp;</li></ol>



<p class="has-text-align-justify">One of the most famous men&#8217;s bags is the backpack, name suggests this bag seat on the back side that’s why called backpack. It’s designed for every lifestyle and features multiple storage compartments, zipper pockets and slots. You can find leather, fabric and all types of colors and designs in this highly versatile and affordable. The backpack is the most versatile of the items on this list and depending on your lifestyle, it could be a smart business-casual accessory, a daily go-anywhere bag for trips to the coffee shop, grocery store or gym or a piece of luggage. Most used for School, college, office, shooting and all. Buy <a href="https://www.shoppersstop.com/carlton-unisex-zip-closure-laptop-backpack/p-205411007/colorChange/205411007_BLUE">Here</a></p>



<ol start="2"><li>CROSSBODY MESSENGER BAG or FANNY PACK &#8211;</li></ol>



<p class="has-text-align-justify">A crossbody messenger bag is worn over one shoulder and positioned so it crosses over the man&#8217;s chest with the bag resting on his side. Some men prefer to carry the bag around their lower back instead of their side. There are many styles for this type of bag, but the most popular feature fold-over flap that is secured at the bottom of the bag with a zipper or closure. This type of bag can hold a laptop, cellphone, pens, papers, and any other items needed. Buy <a href="https://sreeleathers.com/products/161120-leather-waist-bag">Here</a></p>



<ol start="3"><li>TOTE BAG &#8211;&nbsp;</li></ol>



<p class="has-text-align-justify">A large 2-handled open-topped bag (as of canvas). Famous for dangling from the arms of schlepping New Yorkers, tempting patrons at indie bookstores, or holding the groceries of eco-conscious fashionistas, tote bags have been a cultural phenomenon for generations. This versatile bag has evolved past its humble origins to become a signature look from Fashion houses like Balenciaga, Givenchy, Louis Vuitton and more.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-justify">Fashioning a sack out of cotton or leather materials is nothing new, humans have been doing it forever, but what we know as the tote bag&#8211;resplendent in its minimalism and radiant in its practicality—traces its origins back to the verb “to tote”. Popularized in the 17th century, the verb “tote” meant “to carry by hand” or, less gracefully put, “to lug.” While tote bags are traditionally made of canvas, there are no actual limitations to what a tote bag is made of. As long as it can be lugged around, it’s a tote bag!</p>



<ol start="4"><li>LUGGAGE BAG &#8211;&nbsp;</li></ol>



<p class="has-text-align-justify">For trips away, whether on a plane or via a car or train, when you need to carry more stuff with you, nothing beats rolling luggage. It’s too convenient not having to lug around your luggage on your back or by carrying it by the handles when this bag can be gliding effortlessly next to you.</p>



<ol start="5"><li>TOILETRY KIT or DOPP BAG &#8211;&nbsp;</li></ol>



<p class="has-text-align-justify">The final bag or piece of luggage you need is a Toiletry Kit or&nbsp; Dopp kit for all your toiletries and grooming essentials. These are great for trips or for any sort of travel. They keep your stuff organized, are sophisticated-looking and are just a joy to use.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://https://sukantapal.github.io/blog/mens-essential-type-of-bags/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
